eastwestpersonal.com.ph 2015-06-07

# EastWest Bank | Privacy Statement - [EastWestBanker.com]

**EastWest Banking Corporation** is committed to safeguard your privacy online. In general, you can visit EastWestBanker.com without revealing any information about yourself. East West Bank does collect technical information regarding visits to our Web site, such as IP address, browser type, operating system, and average time spent, to measure use, audit logs and improve the content of our site. We analyze these data for trends and statistics to help us provide you with better and secure service.

We will only request information from you, such as your name, address and e-mail address, in order to respond to inquiry, participate in certain promotions, conduct survey, and approve an application to allow access to specific information and services such as the **Internet Banking Facility.**

Any information you provide will be used for EastWest Bank's purposes only. It will not be shared with an individual or other companies, such as direct mail organizations or other third parties, unless required by law. However, EastWest Bank may need to provide your name and delivery address to third parties that East West Bank uses for delivering specific services to you (such as support services or shipping purposes).

**What are cookies and how does EastWestBanker.com use them?**

A cookie is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We do not use "cookies" in order to track your activity on our web site nor gather information concerning your visits to other sites. However, a cookie is stored temporarily when you "Sign In" and is automatically destroyed when you close your browser. Inside this cookie, our system assigns a unique random number not associated with any of your personal information.

The type of cookies that we use are referred to as "non-persistent" cookies because they do not remain on a user's computer hard drive. This temporary cookie expires at the end of the session or closing of a user's browser. We do not use cookies to gather information concerning your visits to other sites, nor ascertain any personal information about you.

**EastWest Bank's Commitment to Privacy and Security**

EastWest Bank maintains a policy of protecting your right to privacy regarding the collection and use of your personal information on the Internet Banking Facility. Our privacy policies are the same whether or not you are a Bank customer, using our Internet Banking services, or you are just visiting EastWestBanker.com. We safeguard the information that you may provide us and we do not collect personal information from anyone who is just visiting our Web site.

Our Internet Banking Facility services are served from a secure server. This means that each page you view and any information you submit is encrypted on its way between your computer and our servers. Even in the highly unlikely event that your transmission is intercepted, it will not be usable by anyone. Your peace of mind and the safeguarding of your information is a top priority for EastWest Bank. All Internet Banking Facility transactions are done through a 128-bit SSL.

Furthermore, we require that you use a unique password to access your accounts and transaction information through our Internet Banking Facility. You can help maintain the security of your personal financial information by not sharing your password with anyone, by changing your password on a regular basis, and by signing off when you have finished your Internet Banking Facility sessions.

**Oversight or Questions**

EastWest Bank welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Statement. As stated above, we are dedicated to protect your privacy and will make reasonable effort to keep your information private and secure. Due to the rapidly evolving changes on the Internet, we may update this Policy Statement and all revisions will be posted to this site. If you have any questions or comments regarding our policy, you can directly contact the [webmaster@eastwestbanker.com](mailto:webmaster@eastwestbanker.com).

 top
